Register of the Aid Refugee Chinese Intellectuals records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Photographs
  - Photo Album #1, ARCI - Hong Kong (Envelopes A-D)
    - 298. Junior graduation day at an ARCI kindergarten for the children of Refugee Chinese Intellectuals.
    - 299. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 300. Welcome for American School and International Women's club delegation.
    - 301. Delegation visiting Juddville.
    - 302. Student body of Chin ling Middle School.
    - 303. Master Tam and Teachers.
    - 304. Singing and playing.
    - 305. Teachers and Students.
    - 306. The office of the School.
    - 307. Basketball.
    - 308. Basketball.
    - 309. Picnic.
    - 310. Athletic meeting.
    - 311. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 312. Blindman's bluff.
    - 313. Kindergarten.
    - 314. Autumn trip.
    - 315. Spring trip.
    - 316. Swing.
    - 317. Sawhorse
    - 318. Travelling to Keng Keo.
    - 319. Travelling to Chin Nau Su.
    - 320. Kindergarden.
    - 321. Primary class.
    - 322. Telling the Christmas Story.
    - 323. Kindergarden children entertain Women's Intl. Club.
    - 324. Kindergarden children entertain Women's Intl. Club.
    - 325. Kindergarden children entertain Women's Intl. Club. American School.
    - 326. Kindergarden for children of armed forces.
    - 327. Sewing clothes & bedding for soldiers.
    - 328. American school.
    - 329. ARCI nurse giving an injection.
    - 330. The new Ford at Juddville.
    - 331. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 332. Libertyville residents after Typhoon Wanda.
    - 333-336. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 337. Backyard after Typhoon Wanda.
    - 338. Backyard banana plantation.
    - 339. New playground in rain.
    - 340-408. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 409. (Photo missing from album).
    - 410. Taking of laryngeal swab.
    - 411. X-ray technician working in dark room.
    - 412. Public health nurse visits patients house.
    - 413. Eyedrops.
    - 414. Going home.
    - 415-419. Dr. Fitch is decorated with Brillant Star by Premier Yui.
  - Photo Album #2 - To Dr. George A. Fitch, with Warm Bon Voyage Wishes from all the personnel of ARCI, Taipei. (Envelope E)
    - 1-2. "Bu Pa Man, Che Pa Chan" - Translated from Chinese red slips -"Don't Fear Slow, But Fear Stop".
    - 3. Translated from Monument, "Fa Yang Min Chu Chun Yi" - "Spread Abroad National Justice".
    - 4. Introductory Card to Album - "To Dr. George A. Fitch, with Warm Bon Voyage Wishes from all the Personnel of ARCI, Taipei".
    - 5-6. (No album captions for these photographs).
    - 7-10. Juddville.
    - 11. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 12-13. Mennonite Christmas Parcel Distributed by Dr. Fitch.
    - 14. Chinese New Year's Celebration.
    - 15-17. Sunday School Nativity Play Christmas Evening.
    - 18. Congressman Walter Judd's Visit,., November 1953
    - 19-22. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 23. Ministers for Juddville.
    - 24. Miss Mary Chen and Friend.
    - 25. Gertrude Su, first Indonesian Student to Graduate from Taiwan University. Now a reporter; she wrote us up.
    - 26. Father of "Baby Moses".
    - 27. Work and Security Staff.
    - 28. Chief of Security.
    - 29-30. W.S. Chen leaves for Job as Chief Surveyor, Kaohsiung Customs.
    - 31-33. Kindergarten and Graduates.
    - 34. Mrs. Moore Signs Guest Book.
    - 35-37. (No album captions - see bakes of photographs for captions).
    - 38. Miss Watney taught Sunday School.
    - 39-42. Children's Party
    - 43-47. Mrs. Maurice T. Moore and Sister arrive at Taipei.
    - 48-51. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 52-57. Mrs. Fitch and Mayor Kao leave for the U.S.
    - 58-62. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 63. Party.
    - 64-65. Distributing Milk Powder.
    - 66-68. Dr. Liu and Nurse Chang in Clinic.
    - 69-70. Senator Margaret Chase Smith leaves Taipei.
    - 71. Leaders. Women's Anti-Aggression League.
    - 72. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 73-75. New Arrivals.
    - 76-80. Madame Chiang's Visit,., Jan. 27, 1959
    - 81-84. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 85-88. USIS Recording at Juddville.
    - 89. FOA Personnel.
    - 90. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 91. Gen. William Chase.
    - 92. Senators Clements and Dirksen.
    - 93-96. FOA Personnel.
    - 97-98. Governor Yen Performs Ribbon-cutting for New Dormitory.
    - 99. Policeman Yao Cares for us.
    - 100. Nurse Chang and County Magistrate Chang.
    - 101. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 102. Map showing location of ARCI Registrants.
    - 103-104. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 105-106. At the Summit: Office of ARCI Four Flights up.
    - 107. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 108. Mrs. Averil Tong, Director of Musicians of Cathay.
    - 109-112. ARCI Team.
    - 113-118. Translators.
    - 119-122. Our Office View.
    - 123-125. People who come to see us - Craft Workers.
    - 126. People who come to see us - Principal Li.
    - 127. People who come to see us - Jen Shan-hsueh, author (photo is missing).
    - 128. People who come to see us - Manufacturer.
    - 129-133. Columbia Luncheon.
    - 134-135. Guerrilla's
    - 136. Just from Hong Kong.
    - 137. Widow left destitute.
    - 138-140. Leadership Training Program - Arrival in Keelung.
    - 141. Leadership Training Program - Listening to Dr. Judd, Noville,., 1953
    - 142-145. Leadership Training Program - English Classes.
    - 146-147. ARCI Donated Buildings.
    - 148-149. Twenty Prize Winners - Essay Contest - Every Essay an indictment of Communism.
    - 150. First Prize Winner.
    - 151. Top Three.
    - 152. Second Prize Winner.
    - 153-155. Awards given at YMCA.
    - 156. Graduate in Provincial Govt. Personnel Dept.
    - 157. Banner Given ARCI by Students.
    - 158. Graduate in Motor Vehicles, Army Training.
    - 159-160. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 161-162. Resettlement and Housing Program.
    - 163. Chia-ya Agricultural School.
    - 164. Hua-lien Industrial School.
    - 165-168. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 169-170. Henry Mi Hsiu, Chief Planner Nitrogen Fertilizer Factory.
    - 171. Real Head hunting Knife - Dr. Brummer trains "Head Hunters" to fill teeth - Price on carved heads. (Photo is missing).
    - 172-173. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 174-177. Pingtung Agricultural College.
    - 178. Pingtung Agricultural College. Registrants.
    - 179. Pingtung Agricultural College. Dr. Raymond Wi's Clinic.
    - 180. Entrance.
    - 181. President Wang with Aborigines-Mountain boys.
    - 182-183. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 184-188. Tainan Industrial School.
    - 189. Model House.
    - 190. Tainan Agricultural School.
    - 191-192. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 193. Tainan Registrants.
    - 194-196. Dr. Fung and Chan, Tainan.
    - 197-199. Tainan Engineering College.
    - 200. Mr. Hsu, Head of All Tainan Scouts.
    - 201-202. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 203-207. Kao-Hsiung Industrial School.
    - 208. Opening the Door! Chang-hwa Girls School.
    - 209-213. Chang-hwa Girls School.
    - 214-218. Taichung College of Agriculture.
    - 219-220. Chu-lan School
    - 221. Wellesley Graduates: Mrs. Han Lih-wu, Daisy Atterbury.
    - 222. (No album caption - see back of photograph for caption).
    - 223-227. Chia-yi Middle School.
    - 228-233. School Principals Visit Us!
    - 234-236. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 237-238. Hong Kong Refugees
    - 239. Rennie's Mill - Hong Kong.
  - Photo Album #3 (No album title) (Envelope F)
    - 1. Graduate Nurse Lee Yiang-Hwa (Reg. No. 25176) and children. (See story).
    - 2. Nurse Li-Yiang-Hwa (Reg. No. 25176) & Baby. A 2nd Lt. Nurse-In-Chief of the 50th Division, New 1st Army, she fled all the way from Changchun, Manchuria and found refuge in Formosa, where she will again continue to serve the Nationalist army. 15/5/54.
    - 3. Plaque at TB Center Employees' Dormitory, Taipei.
    - 4. A side view of the TB Center Employees' Dormitory, donated by TB Association and ARCI.., August, 1954
    - 5. Front view of TB Center Employees' Dormitory, donated by TB Association and ARCI.., August, 1954
    - 6. Scene of TB Center Employees' Dormitory, donated by Taiwan TB Association and ARCI.., August, 1954
    - 7. A side view of TB Center Employees' Dormitory, donated by Taiwan TB Association and ARCI.., August, 1954
    - 8-12. Farewell! Madame Senator!
    - 13-15. Visit to Juddville.
    - 16-33. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).
    - 34. Farewell party given to the last group of students, who left her. 7/11.
    - 35-57. (No album captions - see backs of photographs for captions).